2peer.com 2016-11-05

# 2Peer - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**   |   Terms of Use  |   Copyright

ToPeer Corporation respects and values your privacy. 

This Privacy Policy covers your use of any software that ToPeer Corporation (herein referred to as "ToPeer") makes available to users of the Service (the "Software"), and your use of the ToPeer Websites located at http://www.2peer.com and http://www.topeer.com (the "Sites"). The Service, the Software, and the Sites are collectively referred to as the ToPeer Network ("ToPeer Network"). 

Please read the following to learn more about the ToPeer Network Privacy Policy which is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share with ToPeer. 

We will only collect, store and use your personal information for defined purposes. We use your information to support and enhance our relationship with you, for example, to provide service and support, and share product, service and company news with you. We do not sell your personal information. We only share your personal data outside the ToPeer family of companies with your consent, as required by law or to protect ToPeer, its customers, or the public, or with companies that help ToPeer fulfill its obligations with you. At any time you may contact ToPeer with any privacy questions or concerns you may have. You also may ask at any time to see the data you have given us and request correction, modification, or deletion of your information. 

Your right to privacy and data security is a primary concern to us, that's why, whether you are using a product or service from us or obtaining technical support, whether online or over the phone, or simply visiting [2Peer.com](http://2peer.com/), we strive to ensure that every customer experience is safe and secure. 

ToPeer has prepared this Privacy Policy to inform you about our ongoing commitment to ensuring your personal information remains accurate, confidential and is used only for identified purposes, regardless of how it is provided to us. This policy covers ToPeer's treatment of personal information collected through the use of ToPeer products and/or services, your control of your personal information, and our use of any personal information that you may provide to us. This Policy also addresses how you can inquire about the personal information we hold about you and how we will respond to such a request. 

**Our Policy**

Our policy is simple: Your personal information belongs to you. You have control over how it is used and, as such, you can modify any information that you have provided by logging into our website and editing your account information. You can visit most areas of our website without telling us about yourself or providing any personal information to us. Occasionally we will ask you for personal information in order to allow you access to certain content on our website. This policy is not applicable to personal information that has been aggregated or made anonymous and no longer specifically relates to an identifiable individual. ToPeer reserves the right to use aggregated or anonymous information in any manner it considers appropriate or necessary form time to time. 

**What is Personal Information?**

Personal information is any information that could be used to identify you, including data that you provide when you register on our website or through the use of our products and/or services (e.g. name, address, email, phone number, etc.) and data about your usage of resources on our website or through the use of our products and/or services. 

**When and Why we request specific Personal Information?**

When you provide information to us, we are able to improve our website content or our products and/or services to serve you better. Our goal is to continually improve the relationship that you have with ToPeer, and personal information allows us to provide you with content that is relevant to you. As well, personal information allows us to inform you of new services and products that may be of specific interest to you. 

We request information from you when you: 

  1. Register on 2Peer.com
  2. Place a request for support, whether over the phone or online
  3. Provide feedback in an online survey or other method in order to help us improve 
    1. the effectiveness of our customer relations, 
    2. our products and/or services. 
  4. Participate in a sweepstakes or promotional offer 
  5. Subscribe to a newsletter or a mailing list 
  6. Request technical support whether online through or via telephone

The type of information we may ask for includes, but is not limited to, your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, type of computer & operating system, and other computer or network and Internet connectivity related information. 

**You can opt-out at any time**

If you do not want us to use your personal information to contact you, please let us know and we will not use it for that purpose. If you are less than 18 years of age, please do not submit any personal information to us. 

**Protecting Your Information**

ToPeer does not transfer, trade or sell personal information to third parties. Occasionally, we may share personal information with our partners for marketing or advertising purposes related to ToPeer services and/or products. For example, we may use a third party for the direct emailing of a newsletter and we would provide personal information for the limited and sole purpose of that direct email. 

We will disclose personal information to third parties if, and only if: 

  * We have your consent to do so,
  * We are obliged by a valid court order or you violate our Terms of Use, or 
  * We need to share information to provide you with the products and/or services that you request.

**Personalized Experience**

Everyday new technologies are emerging that help us deliver a more personal experience to you when you visit our website or through the use of our products and/or services. At ToPeer, we primarily use "cookies" to help us determine which service and support information is appropriate to you and/or your computer. Our use of .cookies. does not mean that we automatically know any information about you. Our use of cookies is meant only to enhance your experience when visiting our website or using our products and/or services. ToPeer has no desire or intent to infringe on your privacy by using this technology. .Cookies. are small data files that a website can locate on a visitor's hard drive to monitor site usage. Cookies contain information that you provide, such as your username and password. We use cookies on our site to help us understand what pages are frequently visited and to improve the website experience. A cookie cannot affect data on your computer and cannot provide us with information about other sites you have visited. 

You can set your web browser to not accept cookies or to warn you before accepting a cookie. If you wish to access secured sections of our website, such as the Members section, you will have to enable per-session cookies in your web browser. You can access most of our website without accepting a cookie. 

**Your Consent to the Collection, Use and Disclosure of Your Personal Information:**

The provision of your personal information to ToPeer means that you agree and consent that we may collect, use and disclose your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In addition, from time to time and where appropriate, ToPeer may request your specific authorization or consent. 

If you choose to withdraw your consent, and for certain reasons, ToPeer is unable to comply with your request, we will always advise you that we cannot do so. These could include reasons such as: 

  1. you have selected a payment option for your purchase of one of our products and/or services and we require use of your personal information in order to continue processing your monthly payments;
  2. withdrawing your consent would result in our inability to fulfill the terms of your contract for products and/or services with us; or
  3. there are legal requirements for the use of your personal information.

Please be aware that in certain circumstances, ToPeer may be required to disclose your personal information without your consent such as to law enforcement or other government officials. This could arise, for example, where disclosure is required: 

  1. to comply with a subpoena, warrant or order made by a court with jurisdiction to compel the production of such information;
  2. to legal authorities for the detection and prevention of fraud or other criminal activity; or
  3. to our legal counsel in the event that any matter may be the subject of litigation.

If ToPeer should be required to release your personal information without your consent, such as for the reasons listed above, we would always keep a record of what information was released, to which party it was released and why the circumstances necessitated such release. In order to respect your privacy to the fullest extent possible, ToPeer will only release the information to the extent that we have to. 

ToPeer will not disclose your personal information to any outside organization for its use in marketing without your consent. 

Should the ownership of all or substantially all of the ToPeer business, or individual business units owned by ToPeer, were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy. 

Information regarding you (such as name, address and phone number) or your order and the products and/or services you purchase will not be given to any outside organization for its use in marketing or solicitation without your consent. Under no circumstances do we sell our customer's personal information to third parties. 

**For How Long and Where Does ToPeer Keep My Personal Information?**

We keep personal information only so long as is needed in order to meet the purposes set out in this Policy, including enabling us to meet any legal or regulatory requirements. ToPeer has retention standards for customer information and records management which set out these timelines. We have retention policies in place that govern the destruction of personal information. 

The principal places in which ToPeer holds personal information are in Ottawa, Ontario and nearby municipalities where off-site storage facilities may be located. 

**Third-Party Sites**

Please be aware that other web sites that may be accessed through our site or through the use of our products and/or services may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those third-party web sites linked from 2Peer.com are not covered by this privacy statement. 

You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords or any account information provided either with respect to third party sites or ToPeer passwords/accounts. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

**Contacting ToPeer Corporation**

If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy or any other general inquiries, please contact us by using our online form or by writing to us at the following address; 

ToPeer Corporation  
99 Fifth Avenue, Suite 334  
Ottawa, Ontario K1S 5K4  
CANADA  

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify our Privacy Policy at any time. In the event that we change our privacy policy or our information collection and use practices, we will post a notice on our website. 

Last updated July 2008
